It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
My heart is pounding.
ドキドキしてる
Are you excited?
ドキドキしてる?
Why are you so excited?
なんでドキドキしてるの?
You won't know.
知らなっちゃうよ
That's right.
そうだよね
All of a sudden, I was nervous because the camera was being used like this.
急にね、こんなカメラ回されて緊張したよね
I can imagine what I'll do next.
これから何するか想像つきます
How old are you now?
今何歳?
I'm 19 years old.
19歳です
What do you usually do?
普段は何してるんだっけ?
I'm an idol.
アイドルやってます
How long have you been doing it?
どのくらいやってる?
About a little bit.
ちょっとぐらい
fun?
楽しい?
It's really fun.
めっちゃ楽しい
Shall we have a live show?
ライブしちゃう?
Do you do it every week?
毎週やる?
Every week.
毎週
Does it depend on the event?
イベントによるか
Too.
も ね
Is that something?
それ何かあれ?
Local?
地方の?
Like a local idol?
ご当地アイドル的な?
Where are you doing it?
どこでやってるの?
I usually do it in Fukuoka, but sometimes I do it in Tokyo.
いつもは福岡でやってて、 たまに東京
in.
で
It's called a handshake event.
握 手会言うんだ
Cheki party or something.
チェキ会とか
Can I go?
行っていいですか?
picture?
え?
What should I do?
どうしようかな?
Awkward?
気まずい?
But I'm happy.
でも嬉しいです
happy?
嬉しい?
What about your boyfriend?
彼氏は?
I'm not there.
いないです
Are you being told that you're not there?
いないって言わされてる?
Isn't that just what the agency told you to do?
事務所から言わされてるだけじゃない?
Are you really not there?
本当にいない?
Have you ever done anything naughty?
エッチなことはしたことある?
I've done naughty things.
エッチなことはしたこと
It's been raining quite a bit.
だいぶ豪雨沙汰ですね
Heavy rain?
豪雨沙汰?
I wonder if I did it last?
最後にしたのかな?
It's a little scary to count.
ちょっとカウントするの怖いくらい
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Student days?
学生時代?
High school days?
高校時代?
When you were in high school?
高校生の頃?
Is he a person?
彼、人?
How many people have experience?
経験人数は?
Only that person.
その人だけ
Alone?
一人?
Isn't that what they're saying too?
それも言わされてるんじゃない?
Well, see you then.
うーだね、じゃあね
But wow, I just heard that it's naughty.
でもすごいさっき聞いたら エッチなの
A little naughty.
ちょっとエッチ
You're so horny in your head.
頭の中エッチだよね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
YouTuber.
ユーチューバー
You're going to have sex alone, right?
一人エッチするんでしょ
When do you do it?
どういう時にするの?
Suddenly, I suddenly got a little horny and went to a commercial facility.
ふとした時に 急にちょっと ムラムラしちゃって 商業施設のト
I ran into the bathroom and was alone.
イ レに 駆け込んで 一人で
In the toilet of a commercial facility?
商業施設のトイレに?
When I was shopping at Parco.
パルコとか行った時に 買い物をしてる時に
Are you going to the toilet?
ト イレ行くの?
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Do you want to touch it?
触るの?
I'm literally writing.
文字文字してる
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
On the contrary, it makes me nervous.
逆に緊張するんだけどな
Too many applications.
申請すぎて
I really like your face.
すげえ顔いいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's Aires after all.
や っぱアイレスだね
Is there something?
何かあるの?
A fixed line, or rather a fixed line?
決め台詞っていうか 決め台詞?
There's something going on.
何かあるじゃん
Time introduction.
時間紹介
Decisive line.
決め台詞
Well, I'd like you to think about it with me for a moment.
じゃあちょっと 一緒に考えてほしい
What color?
何色?
There are colors, right?
色あるでしょ?
There are colors.
色ある
white?
白?
Come and match it.
合わせてきて
That's right.
そうなんだ
this is?
これは?
So it's white.
それで白だね
This is dangerous.
やばいじゃん、これ
I'm glad I'm not a fan.
俺がファンじゃなくてよかったのよ
good.
よかった
There's a cute girl.
可愛い少女がいる
Sea shipping is good, isn't it?
海遣いがいいよね
Physically too.
物理的にも
Physically?
物理的にも?
Yeah.
うん
What do you think about when you do that?
そう何する時とか、どんなこと考えるの?
Like watching naughty videos.
ちょっと エッチな映像見たりとかさ
Like AV?
AVみたいな?
Wipe salt or something.
塩拭きとか
Do you get excited when you see salt wipes?
塩拭き見ると興奮するの?
Have you ever wiped with salt?
塩拭いたことある?
Just once.
一 回だけ
Only once?
一回だけ?
Was it wiped?
拭かされた?
If you touch me too much, it will feel good.
あんまり触られすぎると気持ちよくなっちゃう
Is that so?
そうなの?
Is it better not to touch it?
触らないほうがいい?
Do you want me to touch you?
ちょっと触って欲しい?
I just discovered something.
なんか今発見した
It's really scary though.
めっちゃ怖いんだけど
Will you touch me?
触ってくれるの?
What should I do?
どうしよう
I'm confused.
困惑してる
Are you confused?
困惑してる?
I'm touching nature.
自然に触っちゃってる
The way you touch it is amazing.
触り方がすごい
I don't know what to do.
どうしたらいいか分からない
What should I do?
どうしよう
I'm confused.
困惑してる
I'm touching nature.
自然に触っちゃってる
I don't know.
知れない
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I don't know what to do
どう したらいいか分から
do not have.
ない
It feels so good.
気 持ちいい感じちゃう
oh
お
Pai.
っぱ い
Is it on your clothes?
服の上かな?
I have to touch it.
触ってなきゃ
That's a cute outfit.
可愛い服だね
favorite.
お 気に入り
It's really white.
め っちゃ 白いな
It's pure white.
真っ白だね
Smooth.
すべすべ
I think I'll forget.
忘れそうだよね
Take care of it too.
手入れもね
Ah, that's embarrassing.
あ、恥ずかしい
Idol's.
アイドルの
It's dangerous, it's dangerous.
やばいやばい
Embarrassing, embarrassing.
恥ずかしい恥ずかしい
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしい
I have to study.
勉強しないといけない
It smells like lavender.
ラベンダーの匂いがする
Lavender's feet.
ラベンダーのさ、 足でさ
I get nervous and my legs give out.
緊張して足がくくくしちゃう
I'm nervous.
緊張しちゃう
I think we need to move on from now on.
これからいろいろ動いていかないとね
I have to study.
勉強しないといけない
picture?
え?
Win-chan.
ウィンちゃん
Oh no, I just realized it.
やばい、今気がついた
Are you being filmed?
撮られてる?
Maybe.
もしかして
Being photographed.
撮られてる
I've been taking pictures all the time.
ずっと撮ってるよ
It's pure white.
真っ白に真っ白だね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm a little sweaty.
ちょっと汗ばんでる
My hands.
手が
I'm nervous.
緊張して
It makes me nervous.
緊張するよね
terrible.
やばい
It might be really wet.
本当 に濡れてるかも
What should I do?
どうしよう
It might be wet.
びしょびしょかもしれない
What should I do?
どうしよう
It might be very wet.
めっちゃ濡れてるかも
What should I do?
どうしよう
I'm so wet.
めっちゃ濡れてる
It's dangerous, it's dangerous.
やばいやばい
This is terrible.
やばいです
What should I do?
どうしよう
I want to see it from behind.
後ろから見たい
why?
なんで?
behind.
後ろ
oh yeah.
そうそう
Close your legs.
足閉じて
yes.
そう
Is this okay?
これで いいんですか?
soles of feet.
足の裏
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
beautiful.
綺麗
Yeah.
うん
You do something like this, right?
こういうのやるでしょ?
Idol.
アイドル
picture?
え?
I won't do it.
やらないよ
Why don't you do it?
やらないの?
Okay.
いいよ
Pure white.
真っ白で
It's totally curvy.
全然プリプリだよ
It feels real.
リアルに感じてる
Really?
リアルに?
It feels real.
リアルに感じてる
A little amazing.
ちょっとすごい
This height.
この身長
It's too cute though.
可愛すぎるんだけど
It's you.
お前ね
feel the height
身長さを感じて
Rushi.
る し
Give me a break.
休憩してくれ
Oh no.
やば
Is it correct?
当たってる?
Really.
めっちゃ
amazing.
すごい
forever?
ずっと?
But then, come on.
でもさ、じゃあさ
Don't take it off.
脱いちゃえね
picture?
え?
Shall I take it off?
脱いちゃう?
Can't you see?
見えないの?
this?
これ?
Don't look all the time.
じゅるじゅる見ないで
You can go from below.
下からいけるんだね
There's still the most.
まだ一番あるね
There's still the most, right?
まだ一番あるでしょ、それ
Folded neatly.
綺麗にたたんだ
It came out.
出てきちゃったね
terrible.
やばい
Don't look all the time.
じゅるじゅる見ないで
I'm watching it a lot.
めっちゃ見てるよ
Is it facing backwards?
後ろ向いてるかな?
It looks like a tea bag.
ティーバッグみたいになってる
I completely forgot.
ふっかり忘れた
This is what's been happening lately.
最近こうなってる
I don't know what to do.
どうしたらいいか分かんない
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だね
No.
ダメだ
Will it be in a swimsuit?
水 着になったりするの?
When I go to the pool with friends.
友達とプール行ったりする時はね
Because it makes me nervous.
緊張するから
It's up.
アップだ
アップだよ
I think I can get it.
取れそう
I can take it.
取れちゃいす
I can't take it.
取れない
It's beautiful, after all.
綺麗だね、やっぱり
What should I do?
どうしたらいい?
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗だね
Really.
ほ んとに
I don't know.
分かんない
Don't you understand?
分かんない?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I don't like it.
嫌
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I don't like it.
嫌だー
It's a big fetish.
大きいフェチなんだよ
Is it okay?
大丈夫 かな?
It's okay, right?
大丈夫でしょ
I'm sweating so much.
めっちゃ汗かいてる
I need to check it out.
チェックしないと
No, no.
ダメ、ダメ
I'm writing a little bit.
ちょっとかいてるね
I was writing a little.
ちょっとかいてたね
Well, it's a little warm here, too.
あれ、ここもちょっと すげえあったかいんだけど
I don't like it.
嫌だー
I'm sweating.
汗かいてる
Aren't you sweating?
汗かいたんじゃないの?
Hey.
ねえ
It's hot, isn't it?
暑いでしょ
暑いよね
I'm going to sleep a lot.
めっちゃ寝ちゃうから
It's hot.
暑いからね
Because it's difficult.
難しいから
Wait, wait.
待って、待って
It's so beautiful.
すっごい綺麗だね
Because it's difficult.
難しいから
What a pose.
なんてポーズだ
What a pose!
なん てポーズだ
There may be a photo book in the future.
写真集で今後あるかもしれない
Hey.
ねえ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
Should I take care of it a little?
ちょっとお手入れしてきた方がいいですか?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Don't take care of it.
お手入れしないで
You usually do that, right?
普段してるでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
But maybe I should try it again properly.
でもなんか、 ちゃんともう一回やった方がいいかも
I came in the morning.
朝やってきたけど
let's go?
行こう?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's an embarrassing pose.
恥ずかしいのポーズだ
It's a great pose.
すごいポーズしてるからね
It's kind of small.
なんかちっちゃいね
I don't know what my size is.
わかんない、その自分のサイズは
I don't know.
わかんない
No, it looks small though.
いや、見るからにちっちゃいんだけど
I don't see it because I think it's me.
自分だと思うんで見ないから
I don't know.
わかんないよね
Like this.
こんなね
Hey, I just opened it.
ちょっとさ、 今俺が開いたけどさ、
Open it yourself.
自分でさ、 こう開いて
Open it yourself?
自分で開く?
Open it yourself.
自分で開く
My body is stiff!
体硬っ!
Open the photo and do it yourself.
写真開いて、 自分でこう
Like this?
こうやって?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
this.
これ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
this.
これ
It's not okay.
大丈夫じゃないよ
Something amazing is happening.
すごいことなってるよ
Looks delicious.
美味しそうだね
It's so delicious.
すごい美味しい
I want you to open it.
開いてほしい
enter
入
Let's go.
っちゃ う
I'm going in.
入っちゃう
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Why did you remove it?
なんで外した?
No.
ダメ
ダメだよ
fun.
楽しみ
It's small.
ちっちゃいね
I'm going in.
入っちゃう
Small.
ちっちゃい
Oh no no no.
あーダメダメ
I'm going in, I'm going in.
入っちゃう入っちゃう
book
本
I don't want you to get carried away.
気 で入れてほしくない
Did you want it included?
入れてほしくなっちゃった?
what?
何?
banana?
バナナ?
It's so tight that I feel like I'll break my fingers.
めっちゃ指折れそうにきついんだけど
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Sorry
ごめんな
Sai.
さい
cute.
か わいい
So cute.
めっちゃかわいい
I was surprised.
びっくりした
It felt so good.
めっちゃ気持ちよくて
What should I do?
どうしよう
Where can I take the picture?
どっから撮ってもいい?
What should I do?
どうしよう
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm curious.
気になってしまう
I'm seriously observing it though.
マジマジで 観察してるけど
Feels good.
気持ちいい
You're good at it.
上手だね
good?
上手?
It’s been a while
久し
It's Buri.
ぶ りだ
long time no see.
久しぶり
amazing.
すごい
I want it.
欲しくなっちゃう
What should I do?
どうしよう
That's amazing.
すごいね
where?
どこ?
or
や
Bye.
ばい ね
That's amazing.
すごいね
That's terrible.
やばいね
What is dangerous?
やばいって何?
amazing.
すごい
It's dangerous though.
危ないんだけど
I feel like I'm going to go there.
行 っちゃいそうになっちゃう
big.
大きい
I can't take it anymore.
もう我慢できないんだけど
I'm about to go.
行きそうになっちゃってる
So cute.
かわいいっすね
I've said it many times.
何回も言うけど
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm so embarrassed that I'm the one taking the picture.
自分が撮ってるのにめっちゃ恥ずかしい
What should I do?
どうしようか
I want you to include it.
入れてほしい
I want you to enter it.
入 れてほしい
I want you to include it.
入れてほしい
What should I do?
どうしようか
what?
何?
What is this?
これって何?
Are you angry?
怒って?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
Where do you want your dick to go?
ちんちんどこに入れてほしい?
Should I just put it in like this?
このまま入れちゃう?
It might feel good.
気持ちいいかもしれないし
It's not in yet.
まだ入ってないよ
I'm trying to bring it in.
入れてこようとしてる
tight.
きつい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's really tough though.
めちゃくちゃきついんだけど
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's super tight though.
超きついんだけど
I don't know.
わかんない
Are you being harsh?
自分がきついかどうか
I don't know.
わか んないけど
It's hard.
き つい
Wait, that.
待って、それ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'm going in.
入っちゃう
I just put it in.
入れただけだよ
It's really tight.
すごいきつい
I'm going in.
入っちゃう
I just put it in.
入れただけだよ
What feels best?
一番気持ちいいかな?
air
気
It lasts a long time.
持 ちいい
TRUE?
本当?
amazing.
すごい
tight.
きつい
I might go in.
入っちゃうかも
What should I do?
どうしよう
I'll go in right away.
すぐ入っちゃう
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Isn't it early?
早くない?
I went in.
入っちゃった
I'm going in.
入っちゃう
go.
行く
No more.
もうダメ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels really good.
や っぱ気持ちいい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
No, I'm going in.
ダメ、入っちゃう
How many times have you said that?
何回言ってるの?
No.
ダメだよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Let's hold your feet.
足抱えておこう
here?
ここ?
What is this?
何これ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'm going in.
入っちゃう
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's so cute.
め っちゃかわいい
terrible.
やばい
Can I use various systems?
いろんな体制していい?
amazing.
すごい
What should I do?
どうしよう
Again
またなって
Have you ever done that?
した ことある?
what?
何?
I can't move everyone.
皆さんに動けない
I've never done it before.
全然やったことない
What should I do?
どうしよう
I don't know how to move.
どうやって動いたらいいか分からない
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
It's crunchy.
カクカクしてる
Feels good.
気持ちいい
go.
行く
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Super cute.
超かわいい
I'll go in again.
また入っちゃう
Feels good.
気持ちいい
go.
行く
I'm sweating.
汗かいてる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
What should I do?
どうしよう
Open your legs a little.
足ちょっと開いて
Move it in and out slowly.
ゆっくり出し入れして
Looks good.
よく見える
Shaking.
ガクガクする
It's shaky.
ガ クガクするね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'll get it again.
またそれ入っちゃう
go.
行く
Feels good.
気持ちいい
go.
行く
Let's go in again
また入っちゃ
cormorant.
う
What should I do?
どう しよう
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'm already in.
もう入っちゃった
No way.
やだ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Shoulder peter.
肩ペター
Turn your hips away.
腰をそらして
Feels good.
気持ちいい
The air is hot.
空気が熱い
Is there air?
空気入ってる?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
go.
行く
I'm going in.
入っちゃう
Is it in?
入ってる?
No, it's embarrassing.
ダメ、恥ずかしい
Let's go in again
また入っちゃ
cormorant.
う
I can't stand it.
我 慢できない
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I just can't hold it back any longer.
もうちょっと我慢できないんだけど
What should I do?
どう しよう
I can't stand it any longer.
もうちょっと我慢できない
Can I hold back?
我慢していい?
Just like that.
そのまま
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'll go in.
入っちゃうね
go.
行く
I want to come too.
俺も来たいんだけど
Yeah.
うん
I want to come too.
俺も来たい
Will you go with me?
一緒に行ってくれる?
Yeah.
うん
Can I take it out like this?
このまま出していい?
Yeah, let it out.
うん、出して
I want to bring out a lot of good things.
いいのいっぱい出したいの
Can I take it out?
出していいの?
What is this?
なんだこれは?
I'm surprised.
びっくりしちゃう
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
amazing.
すごい
I keep going.
行きまくりじゃん
Me, while sitting.
俺、座りながら
while sitting.
座りながら
Can you get through this?
こっち抜ける?
Are you sitting?
座ってある?
The bottom is standing.
下は立ってある
Is the bottom standing?
下は立ってある?
Ah, then.
あ、じゃあ
Doesn't it look really tacky when you're standing up?
下は立っているときって、めっちゃダサくないですか?
Isn't it really lame?
めっちゃダサくないですか?
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
It's erotic.
エロいよ
Is it okay to be erotic?
エロでいいんですか?
It's a hobby.
趣味なんで
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Isn't that a pervert?
変態ですよね?
It's a pervert.
変態です
I like perverts.
変態好きです
Do you like perverts?
変態好き?
yes.
はい
Hey, look here.
ちょっと、こっち見て
On this side.
こっち側に
It's a beautiful voice.
綺麗な声ですよ
Can I do it anywhere?
どこなりにしてもいいですか?
It felt good when I touched it.
触っていると気持ちよくなったよね
why?
なんで?
Wouldn't it be better if you came with me?
一緒に来てくればよかったかな?
not at all.
全然
Anga?
あんが?
I wonder if there is.
ないかな
not at all.
全然
Isn't it beautiful?
綺麗でしょ?
close.
近い
Like this.
こんな感じで
Is this how you wash it?
こんな 感じ で 洗うの?
It's a little more garish.
もうちょっとガリマサですよ
Garimasa?
ガリマサ?
The leg side is open.
足側が開いて
It's a little cold, so this is the place.
ちょっとひんがないから、ここがひん
Swollen?
ふくられてると?
Yeah.
うん
Uranandall would be fine though.
ウランドオールでいいんだけど
Is it white?
白いのなんですか?
白いの?
It's a bit of a body fork.
ちょっとボディフォークだよ
What is it?
どうなんだ?
Are you washing your clothes here?
こっちで洗ってますか?
not at all.
全然
For general skin.
一般肌用の
Absolutely not.
絶対ない
Is it waterproof?
防水ですか?
It's not waterproof at all.
全然防水じゃない
Isn't that scary?
やばいじゃないですか?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's not waterproof at all.
全然防水じゃないから
Something electric
なんか電
I usually sleep in my car, but I was feeling nervous today.
車 でいつも寝るんですけど、 今日緊張してて
I couldn't sleep at all.
全然寝れなくて
Seriously?
まじで?
My eyes were pounding until morning.
朝まで目バキバキでした
Seriously?
まじで?
That's what I thought.
そんな思いで
You really appreciate it.
本当にあってくれてるんだね
But it was okay.
でもよかった
Was it cool?
かっこよかったかな
It was good.
よかったです
Really.
本当に